Hey y'all and welcome back to Living in
Central Texas. Today I'm giving you an
exclusive tour of this brand spanking
new community right here in Temple,
Texas called Wilma's Way.
[Music]
So, some of my favorite things about
this community are they're just getting
started. There are only 25 lots in this
community. And as far as construction
goes, this is about as far along as they
are in here on about four or five homes.
So, the rest are just empty vacant lots
that if you're interested in building,
um, you can pick a lot. Uh, pick the
floor plan. Again, this is just
exclusive to this builder. And you can
make a lot of those selections still.
So, it's a really great opportunity if
you're looking for a beautiful,
beautiful um mid range, mid-pric range
home beautifully located in Temple,
Texas. So, this community again has 25
lots for sale. It's located right off of
West Adams, which is that main street
through the Temple Belton area. You're
in Temple, city of Temple, but Belton
ISD, if that is important to you, that
school district tax rate as of last year
was 2.27.
And there will be an HOA here. They're
just getting that established, but a lot
lower than most. Um, you know, HOA costs
are going to be a lot lower than a lot
of other states. So, if you hear that
and that scares you, but you're still
open to the idea of an HOA, don't let
that number scare you. Our HOA costs
here are actually pretty low.
Um, okay. So, let's see. So, even though
this one is just getting started, I'm
going to take you over to another
community that this builder's building
in called Wildflower Country Club. It's
just on the golf course and it's only 5
minutes away. So, we'll circle up there
so I can walk you through a few of this
builder's floor plans so you can get a
good feel of how things look on the
inside and outside and all of the
selections that they just build. really
standard to this builder and that'll
help you get a really good sense of how
everything looks once it's finished out.
Uh let's see. So, Wilma's Way, you are
right off of West Adams. Um you're
probably 3 minutes away from Walmart. Um
a bunch of really great restaurants on
West Adams, 3 minutes from Starbucks if
you're a coffee junkie. Summer Moon,
Dutch Brothers, 12 minutes away from
downtown Belton, about 15 minutes away
from downtown Temple. You're 10 minutes
away from Baylor Scott and White
Hospital, 15 minutes away from the VA
hospital, 25 to 30 minutes away from
Fort Hood, 10 minutes away from Lake
Belton, one of my absolute favorites.
You're about an hour north of Austin and
about 35 minutes south of Waco. So,
great location, definitely worth a look.
So, as you can see, that's going to be
the entrance. That's Old Waco Road,
which connects right up to West Adams.
They're still doing construction at the
front.
[Music]
And then all of these lots
are available for build.
A lot of these lots actually have no
rear neighbors and no plans for
development.
[Music]
You can see a lot of the trees in the
distance.
We came out here in perfect time with
all the sunflowers
with just a few houses at the end of the
culde-sac being built.
[Music]
And if the wonderful location and
beautiful build isn't exciting enough,
you also get half acre lots. All of the
lots in this community are on a half
acre or more, which is really, really
huge. I would say that is one of the
biggest selling points um is being able
to capitalize on that. So, if you're
maybe thinking of building a pool down
the road or you're just looking for a
little more space and privacy, this
might absolutely be perfect for you. Of
course, with that halfacre lot, you are
going to be on septic. Um, pretty
typical for this area, especially on a
little bit larger lot.
Okay, I've really been excited to show
y'all this community because it checks
so many of the boxes that my buyers are
frequently seeking. Um, those halfacre
lots are very hard to come by for brand
new homes in centrally located in
Temple.
The builder is fantastic. This is a
Kurther's build. A lot of the things
that this builder includes standard as a
standard feature are included in upgrade
for a lot of other builders. The price
point, you're going to be in the
mid500,000s
to upper 600,000s.
you're in Belton ISD, which is our more
desirable school district, highly
soughtafter school district. And the
location just really doesn't get any
better if you're looking to be close to
everything. So, I'm really glad we
jumped on and took a tour as they're
just getting started. Okay, let's go.
Okay, we have arrived. We are standing
in front of a beautiful fully finished
new construction Kurther's home. This
one is in the Wildflower Country Club in
Temple. It's on the golf course. It is
about five minutes away from Wilma's
Way. Uh but super close. Just a totally
different vibe and style. I will do a
totally different video on this
community in particular because I
definitely think it's worth highlighting
and mentioning. But for now, we're just
going to give you a really great glimpse
into what a final product looks like for
this builder. I want you to note that
because this is a different community,
their budgets, standard features do
vary. The elevation, meaning the front
of the home is not going to look like
this. We are on a hill. There are also a
bunch of large oak trees. Wilma's way
doesn't have that. They each have their
own really awesome unique features and
appeal.
This is Kurther's Reagan for floor plan.
It's a 4 bed, 2 and 1 half bath, 2600
square ft, priced at just over 800,000.
Let's take a look.
The builder is definitely offering
incentives in this current moment. If
you'd like to know more about those or
have someone advocate for you, you can
find all my contact information below.
This home sits on the golf course,
threecar garage.
The exterior of the home features
four-sided masonry,
brick and stone,
full saw and irrigation,
and the most regal
walkway up to your front door. I'm
telling you, the curb appeal on this one
is one of a kind.
Everything about this home
is elegant and refined.
It feels super upscale
and polished.
Upon entry, you have a formal dining
space or flex room with a beautiful
chandelier,
accented ceilings,
and a full office with French doors.
All of the secondary bedrooms
and this office include fans.
You'll also notice the crown molding
throughout
and high doors.
I really love what they've done with
this accent wall and the pull- in with
that mossy green accent paint.
This is vinyl plank flooring throughout
[Music]
and carpets in the bedroom.
You have a beautiful electric fireplace
which is accented nicely.
Built-in shelves,
hidden kitchen, a large oversized
island
with quartz countertops.
[Music]
Something unique to this community is
going to be gas. So, if you are looking
for gas cooking,
definitely take note. You have these
glorious stainless steel appliances, a
pot filler, this is really a chef's
dream in here.
Your exhaust is vented out. You have
your farm sink.
Beautiful custom cabinets,
[Music]
two-toned with your center island being
that really pretty stained brown and the
exterior being painted gray with uh
really nice hardware.
Amazing pantry space.
One of my favorite things about this
builder is their attention to detail.
the ceilings, light fixtures, pendants,
hardware,
just all feels super elevated.
This is a split floor plan. We have your
half half bath just off the main living
space.
[Music]
Headed into the primary suite, you have
a private entrance to the patio.
Generous carpet throughout,
recess lighting, fan.
This builder does a fabulous job with
their um primary suite, primary baths.
You have a large soaking tub,
huge walk-in shower
with multiple fixtures,
great cabinet space,
dual vanity,
and one of my favorite features
is this massive walk-in closet. Super
functional.
You have rods all the way to the top if
you'd like to hang your winter clothes.
rotate seasonally.
[Music]
Off of the dining and kitchen space, you
have entry to your garage.
This is your laundry room with a space
for an extra fridge or freezer. Fun
little hexagon tile. And you also have a
utility sink in here. We have your
secondary
[Music]
bedrooms.
Bedroom one.
[Music]
This is your um second bath. All of
these rooms are pretty standard size.
You have good walk-in closets.
Oh my gosh. I think for a
I think for a guest closet, this is
definitely one of a kind. Guest room
facing the street. I did just speak with
the sales rep and he said that there's
not going to be a ton of difference
between this community and Wilma's way.
Let's go take a look at the backyard.
So, you have three entrances to the
backyard. Right off the garage, right
off the living space, and then right off
of the primary suite.
Okay, so you have a massive oversized
patio
with a built-in kitchen, gas grill,
sink,
and wine fridge, beer fridge
right on the golf course
with a gas
fireplace.
You can really picture yourself sitting
out here in the evening
[Music]
enjoying your patio space
watching golf. Really picturesque. And
these are all on halfacre lots as well.
So in terms of size gives you a really
great comparison between these and
Wilma's way. If you would like more
information on this community,
[Music]
reach out and I can get you current
inventory as well as prices, incentives,
and a lot of other helpful information.
And of course, a threecar garage
with two remotes,
pull down stairs.
There is spray foam insulation in this
home. some additional storage space. You
even notice that they paint the garages
in here. Not all builders do that.
If you're thinking about moving here, be
sure to download the free relocation
guide below. It's packed with
neighborhood statistics, videos, and
local insights.
Hey, thanks for checking out Wilma's
Way, this brand new community here in
Temple, Texas. I hope you found it
helpful. If there are any other
communities or areas that are peing your
interest that you'd maybe like more
information on or more YouTube videos
on, leave a message in the comments and
I'll add it to my list of upcoming
YouTube videos. That's always really
helpful for me to know what you're
looking for. And if you would like more
information on relocating to the central
Texas area, head on over to
livingincttx.com
where we have some really fantastic
resources including an interactive map,
relocation guides, and so much more.
Don't forget to like, subscribe, and
click the bell icon so that you can stay
uptodate on all things real estate here
in Central Texas. Till next time.